いや 羨ましいです｡
Some-Stuffs Presents
〈ジョナサンの死から
49年後➡
This elderly gentleman is someone we're quite familiar with.
時は移り
世代も変わる！➡
Or rather, we're familiar with that scar and those eyes.
老師トンペティの
後継者➡
ストレイツォと
その一派！➡
石油王となった
スピードワゴン！➡
It's been too long, Mr. Speedwagon.
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
彼らは これから➡
I've caught wind of your success in
the oil industry since you moved to America.
メキシコに
あるものを 見に行く｡➡
Timing:
Fadeout4
スピードワゴンが設立した
財団の➡
No, it isn't much to speak of.
遺跡発掘隊によって発見された
あるもの！➡
I see the passage of time has been very kind to you.
Typesetting:
Fadeout4
いまだ 世間には
公表されていない➡
I can hardly believe we're the same age.
彼らしか知らない
あるものを！〉
I must say, I'm envious of the benefits
that come along with mastering the Ripple.
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)これから
あなたが目撃するものは➡
Times have changed in the 49 years since Jonathan's death,
and since then, a new era has arrived.
それを見た瞬間 多分…｡➡
Quality Check:
Mazrim
いや 絶対に あなたの背筋に
身の毛のよだつような➡
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Straits has succeeded Master Tompetty,
and he brought along his associates.
恐怖のうずきを
味わわせることでしょう｡➡
Speedwagon has become an oil baron.
50年前 ディオとの戦いで
体験した あの…➡
And together they're off to Mexico, searching for something.
Raw Hunter:
WRRRRY
どす黒い気分以上の うずきを！
It is an object of great interest, discovered by
an archaeological team funded by Speedwagon's company.
Distro:
ExWizzard
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)あっ｡➡
おお…
遺跡の奥に こんな大広間が｡
An object, once hidden from society,
that has been revealed to these men alone!
あなたを呼んだ理由は これです！
こ… これは!?➡
What I am about to show you may come as a surprise.
石仮面！
それも こんなに たくさん！
No, I am almost certain that it will send shivers down your spine!
なっ！
It will fill you with a sense of dread far more terrifying than
anything we felt during our battle with Dio fifty years ago!
Why would a chamber like this exist so deep within these ruins?
This is why I've called upon you, my friend!
Th-That's...
...the stone mask?!
There are more than one?!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
1938 New York
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)《あれは 1938年の秋➡
It all started in the autumn of 1938.
As usual, I was out on the prowl.
俺が いつものように 獲物を
狙っているときのことだった》
Get outta here!
≪(男性)何だって!?
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ん？
(男性)お宅
この飲み物を知らねえだと!?➡
Buddy, don't tell me you've never heard of this drink before!
Pal, I'm just guessing from your English accent...
兄ちゃん そのアクセントだと
イギリス人ぽいね｡➡
...but are you a tourist?
旅行者かい？
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)フッ！
What? Just got here?
(男性)
何？ 引っ越してきたばかりだと？
ふ～ん｡
Either way, you wanna drink, you gotta pay!
ともあれだ！
飲むんなら 金を払いな｡
この国のおきては 金よ｡
That's just how it works here!
ヘイ！ イギリスの兄ちゃん！
Hey! British fella, that kid just ran off with your wallet!
あんたの財布だ！ 追っかけなよ！
ふん！ まぬけが！
ちょろいもんよ！
What a slowpoke, that was a piece of cake!
あっ!?
(警官１)ゲェヘヘヘ！
よお スモーキー｡
Yo, Smokey. Looks like we finally caught ya...
とうとう捕まえたぜ｡
現行犯だ！
...red-handed!
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ヒーッ！
(警官１)この ゴミクズ野郎が！
You damned thieving negro!
ゴホッ ゴホッ！
I could have you rotting in prison for up to twenty years for this!
(警官１)この罪だけで 20年は
出れねえようにしてやるぜ！
Come on, man! It was just a wallet!
許して…
おいら 財布をとっただけだ！
You little shit! Do you have any idea how much I hate you people?!
(警官１)この トンチキが！
俺は てめえらが 大嫌えなんだ｡
But you see, I'm a pretty reasonable guy...
だがな 俺は いいやつなんだ｡
...so just bring me twenty bucks a week...
これから 毎週 20ドルずつ
俺の所に 持ってこい｡
それから 盗んだ物の半分もだ！
...along with half of everything you steal!
うう…｡
Hello?
≪(ｼﾞｮｾﾌ)あの～｡
ん？
(警官１)
何だ 財布とられた まぬけか｡➡
Are you the dolt that got his wallet swiped?
財布は 証拠として
俺が預かっとくぜ｡
I'll need to hold on to it for evidence!
いえ 何ていうか あのですね…｡
Well, actually, I was just gonna say...
...I gave that wallet to him, officer.
その財布は
私が 彼にあげた物ですよ｡
お巡りさん｡
And just like that, this 6'3" Englishman was covering for me!
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)《なんと その195cmは
あろうかというイギリス人は➡
この俺を かばったんだ！》
だから その…｡
Anyway, that said...
...I'd appreciate it if you let him go and gave me back my wallet.
財布も 彼も
放してもらわんと困る｡
What's that?!
何だと!?
I really did give it to him.
確かに あげたんですよ｡
友人なんすよ 彼は｡
We're the best of pals, you see.
Now let him go.
放してやってください｡
(警官１)ほう 友人だと？
Oh! A pal of yours?!
ほ～｡
それじゃ 友人の名を言ってみろ｡
How 'bout you give us his name then?
Don't mess with me!
うそつくんじゃねえ！
お前も ブタ箱に入りてえのか？
Unless you also want to go to prison for obstructing justice!
あ？ ウスノロよォ！
Huh, dumbass?!
(警官たち)デヘヘヘ…｡
I've got a question for you.
聞いていいか？ 分からんのだ｡
I really don't get it, but what's the point in acting like this?
何だって こんなことをする？
What exactly are you trying to accomplish?
この行為に
どんな意味があるっていうんだ？
There is no point!
意味なんてねえ！
I do what I want because I feel like it, you punk!
スカッとするから
してるだけなんだよ！ このボケ！
I already wiped snot on your right cheek, so now let's do the-
右の頬に 鼻くそ付けられたら
左の頬にも…｡
図に乗るんじゃあない！
このポリ公が！
Watch your fucking attitude! You dirty cop!
アンギャーッ！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ああ！
(警官２)ああっ！
Are you trying to resist arrest?!
こいつ 抵抗する気か!?
ケッ！ 撃ってみろ！
Give me your best shot!
だが 覚悟がいるぜ｡
But I'm warning you...
...the moment that hammer cocks,
I'm going to snap your finger in half like a matchstick!
撃鉄を起こした瞬間
てめえの指を へし折る！
マッチみてえにな！
At this range?! I'll blow your goddamned head off!
この距離でか!?
脳天 ぶっ飛ばしてやるぜ！
At that moment, his entire body looked like it was glowing!
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)
《そのとき 俺には 彼の体が
少し 光ったように見えた》
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)《どんなマジックを
使ったのか｡➡
I don't know what kind of magic he used,
but that bottle cap flew off so hard it
smashed that cop's finger into a bloody pulp!
ぶっ飛んだ栓は 圧倒的パワーで
ポリ公の指を 完全にへし折り➡
肉を はじき飛ばした！》
ギャアアース！
はっ！ 思わず カッとなって
また やっちまった！
I can't believe I let my temper get the best of me again!
ま… 参ったな…｡
Oh crap... Granny Erina's gonna let me have it!
エ… エリナばあちゃんに
叱られるぜ！
This guy is nuts!
《な… なんてやつだ｡➡
警官を
こんな目に遭わせたのに➡
He just clobbered a pair of cops,
but he's worried he'll get in trouble with this Granny Erina?
なんと こいつは
エリナばあちゃんとかいう人に➡
叱られることだけを 恐れている》
おい！ そこの ひったくり
早いとこ ずらかろうぜ！
Hey, pickpocket! Let's scram!
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)
《どうやって コーラの栓を
飛ばしたかを聞いたが➡
When I asked him how he shot the bottle cap like that,
he said he didn't know.
知らないということだった｡➡
All he said was he could do stuff like that since he was a kid.
子供のころから
自然にできると言っていた｡➡
何でも 若くして死んだ
彼の祖父が➡
Apparently so could his grandfather, but he died real young.
同じことをできたらしい｡➡
パイロットで戦死した父親は
できなかったとも言っていた》
His dad was a pilot who died in the war, and he couldn't do it at all.
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)
《母親も いないらしかった》
I don't think his mom is alive either.
I really owe ya one...
借りを作っちまったな｡
俺の名は スモーキー｡
The name's Smokey.
名前を聞かせてくれよ｡
What's yours?
Joestar.
ジョースター｡
ジョセフ･ジョースター｡
Joseph Joestar.
♬～
BATTLE TENDENCY
Episode 10: "New York's Jojo"
But you can call me Jojo.
ジョジョって呼んでくれ｡
This is... Who is the man depicted on this pillar?!
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)これは… この柱に
彫られている この男は 一体…｡
This is no ordinary sculpture.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)彫刻ではない｡➡
It contains amino acids and has a cellular structure!
こいつには アミノ酸がある！
細胞がある！➡
There's also a very faint trace of a pulse and body heat!
微妙ながら体温がある！
脈拍がある！
In other words, this thing is alive!
生きているんじゃ こいつは！
え!?
Mr. Straits, I don't care what sort of creature this is,
nor how many thousands of years it's been here.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ストレイツォさん！
こいつが どんな生命体なのか？➡
何千年前からいるのか？➡
Nor do I care why it created the stone masks,
or as to why it was entombed here!
石仮面を作った目的は
何なのか？➡
なぜ ここにいるのか？
そんな謎は どうでもいい！➡
It doesn't matter to me!
あなたを呼んだ理由は
ただ１つ！➡
I called you here for one simple reason;
please use the Ripple to destroy this thing while it remains asleep!
こいつが 眠っているうちに➡
こいつを 波紋法で
完全に 破壊していただきたい！➡
ただ！ それだけですじゃ！
For this, and this alone!
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)
ジョセフ･ジョースターは…｡
Joseph Joestar...
は？
...How is Joseph Joestar?
ジョセフ･ジョースターは
元気かね？➡
I have heard he used the Ripple to aid you in the past.
彼は 以前 波紋で
あなたを助けたことがあるとか？
なぜ 今 ジョジョの話を!?
Why are you bringing up Jojo right now?
As I seem to recall,
this story took place when Jojo was thirteen years old.
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)聞いたのは ジョジョが
13歳のころの話だったか…｡
Yes. I believe the story goes that
your plane was hijacked and you were held hostage.
そう 確か➡
身代金目的で 君の飛行機が➡
ハイジャックされたときの
エピソード｡
(犯人１)おい 小僧！
こんな後ろに いるんじゃねえ！➡
Hey, kid!
You can't be hanging out down here. Now beat it!
前へ行け！
はぁ… ハイジャックされたのは
ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝのじいさんだろ？
You're hijacking old man Speedwagon's plane, right?
一緒にいただけの僕には
関係ないね｡
What's that got to do with me?
ここで 漫画 読んでっから➡
I'll just keep reading my comic,
and you people can finish whatever it is you're doing.
いいから 気にせず
勝手にやってくれ｡
ああ…｡
Watch your mouth, you little snot!
(犯人１)ナマ言うんじゃねえ！
ガキが！
ジョジョ！
Jojo!
あ… ああ…｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)《ま… まずい！➡
This isn't good!
Jojo's not the type to lose his cool over getting hit,
but staining the clothes he got from Erina is a whole different story!
ジョジョは 殴られたことよりも➡
エリナさんに買ってもらった服が
血で汚れたことを 怒るタイプ！》
Keep calm, Jojo!
落ち着くんじゃ ジョジョ！
You idiots wouldn't hijack a plane unless
you were prepared that it might crash, right?
お前ら！
飛行機を乗っ取ったからには➡
墜落するのも 覚悟しての
行動なんだろうな？
(ﾊﾟｲﾛｯﾄ)うあ…｡
なっ!? 今のは… 波紋！
That was... the Ripple!
(犯人たち)う… うわ～！
This kid's insane! He's gonna make us crash!
この小僧 むちゃくちゃだ！
墜落させる気か！
(犯人２)誰か操縦しろ！
(犯人３)誰もできねえ！
Somebody take the stick!
How do I do that?!
じいさん シートでくるまって
飛び降りるぜ！
Pops, grab a seat and get ready to jump!
なっ!?
≪(爆発音)
後先考えずに
むちゃするやつよ｡
That was a foolish stunt to pull without thinking ahead!
I thought about it for a second...
考えているよ｡
少なくとも エリナばあちゃんと➡
At the very least, I thought about protecting you and Granny Erina.
あんたの命だけは
守れる範囲内で｡
僕の たった２人の
家族だもんな｡
You guys are my only family after all...
He may look like Jonathan,
but he's not what you would call a gentleman.
ジョナサンと 顔はそっくりだが➡
性格は
紳士というには 程遠いやつ｡
あのとき 初めて➡
That was when I first learned Jojo could use the Ripple.
わしは ジョジョが
波紋法を使えることを知った｡
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)
祖父ジョナサンから 受け継いで➡
Perhaps Jonathan passed down some of that power to him...
...causing him to be born with
some degree of proficiency as a result.
生まれつき 波紋呼吸法を
身に付けているというわけだ｡
ええ｡
しかし なぜ 今 その話を…｡
Perhaps... But why bring this up now?
W-What are you doing?!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)な… 何を!?
この者たちは 今 私が殺した｡
It looks to me like I just killed these men...
...and once I kill you, Jonathan's grandson will be filled with despair... and rage!
そして 君が死んだら➡
当然 ジョナサンの孫は
悲しみ 怒り➡
He will seek me with a vengeance.
この私に 恨みを抱くだろうな｡
S-Straits-
ス… ストレイ…｡
ぐっ！
Straits...
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ストレイツォ…｡
H-Have you gone mad?!
ち… 血迷ったか…｡
いいや 至って冷静だよ
スピードワゴン｡➡
No, I am actually quite composed, Speedwagon.
I took to the way of the Ripple as a means to preserve my body.
私は 肉体を鍛錬するために
波紋法の道へ入った｡➡
Though ironically, the more one trains,
the more one understands the limitations of their aging body.
だが 修行すればするほど➡
自分の老いていく肉体が
はっきり分かる｡➡
I was ashamed when I realized that I was only barely superior to normal humans.
情けないほどにな｡➡
普通の人間より ほんのちょっぴり
優れているというだけなのだ｡➡
Even the Ripple is incapable of ebbing the flow of time!
波紋法でさえ
この老いは 止められん…｡➡
私は 50年前の戦いのとき
ひそかに ディオに憧れた｡
During our battle fifty years ago, I realized I admired Dio!
His power! His beauty! His eternal youth!
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)あの強さに
美しさに 不老不死に！
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)私も 石仮面の力が
欲しいと思った！➡
I yearned to possess the power of the stone mask for myself...
..so I'll destroy anything that gets in the way of that goal!
他人を 犠牲にしてもな！
Y-You've lost your mind, Straits!
ね… ねじ曲がったか
ストレイツォ…｡
Now allow me to use your blood and obtain my immortality.
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)私は これから
貴様の血で 不死を手に入れる！➡
That will leave Erina Joestar and Joseph as
the only people to know of the mask's existence!
そうすれば この世で
この仮面のことを知るのは➡
エリナ･ジョースターと
その孫 ジョセフのみ｡➡
２人を抹殺したあと
私は ゆっくりと➡
After I've killed them, I'll unlock mysteries
within the stone mask Dio never even dreamed of!
ディオ以上に
石仮面の謎を 究められる！
D-Don't do it...
や… やめろ…｡➡
The stone mask holds terrifying secrets we may never understand!
石仮面には まだ解いていない
恐るべき謎が…｡
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)うおっ！➡
うお～っ！
エリ… ナ… さん｡
ジョ… ジョ…｡
Miss... Eri... na...
Jojo...
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)うお～！
(ﾌﾞﾚｰｷ音)
Hey! Watch where you're walkin', ya dumb brute!
(運転手)おら！ どこ 目つけて
ぶらついとんだよ スカタン！➡
Go get a dog if you want someone to kiss your ass!
てめえのケツ
犬にでも キスさせてろ！
Hurry up and get out of my way you-
早く どきやがれ！ この…｡
うっ うう…｡
もしも～し！
Hello there! Huh, now what was that?!
あ？ 何だって？ ゆっくりと！
Could you repeat that back to me, nice and slow?
もう一遍 言ってみろ！
Maybe in a language I can actually understand?
通訳なしでも 分かるようにな！
場合によっちゃ ぶっ飛ばす！
ひっ！
Watch what you say, or I'll beat you!
≪(ｴﾘﾅ)ジョジョ！
いっ!?
Jojo...
...what are you doing?
(ｴﾘﾅ)何をしているのです？
えっ…｡
エ… エリナばあちゃん！
G-Granny Erina!
What are you doing to that man?
その人に 何をしているのです？
Uh, well...
あ～ え～と…｡
I was just...
そのですね…｡
はっ！ タクシー！
Taxi!
I was just hailing the taxi, Granny Erina!
タクシーですよ
エリナおばあちゃん｡
お～ ジョジョ｡
それは 気が利くわね｡
Oh, Jojo, how very thoughtful of you.
Mr. Smokey, I'd like you to join us.
スモーキーさん
あなたも行きましょう｡
The Joestar family was just an old woman and her grandson...
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)《おばあちゃんと 孫の➡
たった２人だけの一族
ジョースター家》
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)
《おいらが 少しずつ知った
２人の過去は…》
...but slowly, I began to learn about their great legacy.
Say Granny...
なあ おばあちゃん
スピードワゴンはよ➡
...Speedwagon asks us to come on over to New York...
俺たちに ニューヨークに来いって
言っておいてよ➡
どっか 旅行してるんだって!?
いいかげんなやつだなあ…｡
...but now he's off on some trip?!
That's pretty rude, don'tcha think?
I'm sure the life of an oil baron is a busy one.
石油の仕事で
きっと 忙しいのでしょう｡
は～？
ふ～ん…｡
So, Granny...
ねえ おばあちゃん｡
ん？
ホントにさ スピードワゴンは
おじいちゃんの親友だったの？
Honestly now, you only knew Speedwagon as Grandpa's friend?
And that's all? Really?
ただ それだけ？ ホントに？
What are you getting at?
どういうことです？
I mean, the old man is a bachelor.
だってさ
あのじじいは 独身だよ｡
And you've been a widow for a pretty long time.
おばあちゃんも ずっと 未亡人｡
ホントに それだけの
仲なのかな～と思ったりして！
I say this because I'm curious if there was
something "more" between the two of you.
う… 無礼者が！
You foul-minded-!
あだっ！ 分かった！
I get it! I won't mention it-
あだっ！ もう言わない！
おばあちゃん 許して！
Granny, forgive me!
知ってるよ
スピードワゴンの義理堅さは！
I know! Speedwagon's an honorable guy!
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)《ジョースター家は
代々 短命な一族｡➡
The Joestars never seemed to live for very long...
Granny Erina's husband died in some kind of ship accident when she was younger.
エリナおばあちゃんは 若いとき
夫を 船の事故で失い➡
She was pregnant at the time, and her son would
grow up to marry the little girl she rescued that fateful night.
そのとき
みごもっていた 男の子と➡
その 事故のとき
一緒に助かった 女の赤ちゃんが➡
大人になって 結婚して
それが ジョジョの両親｡➡
They were Jojo's parents.
このご両親も 戦死と病気で
亡くなったのだそうだ》
Her son died in the war, while his wife later succumbed to disease.
Granny Erina was one of the nicest people I had ever known.
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)《エリナおばあちゃんは
限りなく優しい｡➡
She was kind not just to me, but to everyone.
チンピラのおいらにも
誰に対しても｡➡
I think it might be because she had such a sad life herself.
それは その人生の
寂しさのせいなのだろうか…》
Jojo was the same.
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)《ジョジョも同じだ｡➡
そして その親切さが その日に
トラブルの元になった｡➡
I think his kindness was what ended up causing the most trouble.
おいらのせいで…》
And it was all my fault...
Waiter! Waiter!
(男性)おい ｳｴｲﾀｰ！ ｳｴｲﾀｰ！
(ｳｴｲﾀｰ)はい｡
Yes, sir?
I didn't know this joint served filthy pigs like him!
(男性)この店は あんな臭え
豚野郎を入れてんのか？
はぁ～!?
(男性)あいつの臭いが
料理に移って まじいんだよ｡➡
He's stinking up the place and ruining my meal!
ああいうのを
入れてんじゃあねえ！
People like him should be kept out!
Sir, it is the policy of this establishment
to allow anyone who can pay to dine here.
(ｳｴｲﾀｰ)お客様 この店では
いかなる お客様でも➡
料金さえ 払っていただければ
料理を お出しいたします｡
Are you shitting me?!
何だと!? この店は
豚が 豚を食ってもいいのか!?➡
You telling me this place lets the pigs dine on pork?!
はぁ～!?
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)お… 俺 先に帰るよ｡
I think I should be going now...
なっ!?
ジョジョ！
おばあちゃん｡➡
Jojo...
Granny, you aren't going to stop me, are you?
まさか
止めんじゃないでしょうね｡
(ｴﾘﾅ)いいえ｡
個人の主義や主張は 勝手！
Hardly.
He may be free to have whatever prejudices he wants...
...but I refuse to forgive such disrespect towards a friend.
許せないのは 私どもの友人を
公然と侮辱したこと｡
Deal with him quickly so as not to disturb the other customers.
他のお客に 迷惑をかけず
きちっと やっつけなさい！
Sounds good to me!
そうこなくっちゃあな｡
(男性)オホホ…｡
やるってのか？ 兄ちゃんよ！
You wanna go, pal?
Hey, big guy!
ヘイ おっさん！
If you're looking for those brass knuckles,
they aren't in your coat pocket!
メリケンサックを
捜しているのなら➡
あんたの上着の
ポケットにゃあないぜ！
ズボンの 後ろポケットに
入っている！
They're in your back pants pocket!
なっ!?
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)えっ!?
えっ…｡
《あっ！ まさか!?》
How did he...
でっ!?
お前は 次に➡
Now you're gonna say "How did you know about my brass knuckles, you punk?"
｢何で メリケンのこと
分かったんだ この野郎！｣と言う｡
How did you know about my brass knuckles, you punk?!
何で メリケンのこと
分かったんだ!? この野郎！
あっ！
お前の利き腕の
指の擦りむけを見れば➡
I could tell from the indentations on your knuckles
that you used them pretty recently.
それは メリケンサックをはめて
ケンカしたものと分かる！
そして お前のシャツに
付いているのは 血！
There's also blood on your shirt.
A splatter of blood!
それも 返り血！
You were just recently beating someone up, weren't you?
さっき
人を殴ってきたばかりだな？
そして 血が上着ではなくて➡
So the blood on your shirt can only mean one thing;
you took your coat off before beating them!
シャツに
付いているということは➡
上着を脱いで
ケンカしてきたということ！
うう…｡
In short, doesn't it only make sense for you
to have put it in your back pocket and not your jacket?
つまり メリケンサックを
指から外したとき➡
上着は着てないから ズボンの
ポケットにしまったことは➡
当然の結果だ！
ぬう…｡
次のせりふは ｢分かったから
どうだってんだよ？➡
Now you're gonna say "What does it matter, you little shit?"
このくそガキが！｣だ｡
分かったから どうだってんだよ？
このくそガキが！➡
What does it matter, you little shit?!
当たった！
How does that feel?!
ぬががぁぁぁぁ ハーッ！
ざまあみろ
カッコつけんじゃあねえ！
That's what you get for being such a smartass!
いいや 違うね｡
What are you going on about?
一体 どこ殴ってんだよ｡
And what the hell were you hitting?
お前が 楽しそうに殴ってたのは
俺じゃないぜ｡
Because whatever you were just fist fighting with, it wasn't me.
デッ！ アガダァーッ！
お前のような
単純 脳みその やるパターンは➡
Can't you see how easy it is for me to read idiots like you?
全て 読まれてるってこと
分かんねえのか!?
Got that? You damned idiot!
この うすバカが！
(客たち)お～！
Please excuse the behavior of my associate.
(ﾏﾌｨｱ)いや！
子分の無礼を 許してください｡➡
Madam, you're Erina Joestar, correct?
マダム あなたは
ｴﾘﾅ･ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰさんでしょう？
私は スピードワゴンさんに
大変 世話になってやしてね｡
Mr. Speedwagon has helped me out of a fix or two.
He told me all about you, back when we were in London.
あんたのことも 以前 ロンドンで
教えられて 知ってるんですよ｡
会えてよかった｡➡
I'm glad I've found you.
I have some underground information that
hasn't been revealed to the public just yet.
実は さっき知った 裏の情報で➡
まだ この国の新聞屋とかには
知られてねえんだが｡
Mr. Speedwagon has been murdered.
スピードワゴンさんが
殺されましたぜ｡
ああ…｡
なっ!?
What was that?
何… だと!?
According to current rumors, the culprit was a monk from Tibet.
(ﾏﾌｨｱ)うわさでは やったのは
チベットから来た 修行僧｡
A monk? Was it Straits?!
修行僧… ストレイツォか！
Apparently the bodies of Speedwagon and
a few others were found on a river bank in Mexico.
(ﾏﾌｨｱ)
メキシコ奥地の川で 流れ着いた➡
スピードワゴンと その一行らしい
死体を発見した者の話だ｡➡
どこで なぜ殺されたのかも➡
Nobody knows for certain who did it, and we are
also unsure as to the current whereabouts of this monk.
修行僧が どこへ行ったかも
誰も知らない｡
(ｴﾘﾅ)わ… 分かるような気がする｡
I think I understand...
きっと 多分
スピードワゴンさんが➡
This... must be about the story Mr. Speedwagon told me,
about Dio and the stone mask.
かつて 話してくれた
石仮面と ディオ…｡
それに まつわることのような
気がする｡
Jojo, that guy's from the Mafia!
ジョジョ…
この男は マフィアだぜ！
信用しちゃあいけねえ｡
きっと たかろうとしてるんだ！
You can't trust him. He's probably up to no good!
そう思うのは 勝手よ｡
Whatever suits you.
Fella, your lighter's in your breast pocket.
おっさん！ ライターなら
胸ポケットに入ってるぜ｡
あっ…｡
スモーキー！
Smokey, I appreciate the warning,
but I'm almost positive this guy is telling the truth!
忠告はありがてえが 俺は
こいつの言うことを 信用する｡
The only thing that motivates these guys is money!
こいつらは
銭金のみで動く連中｡
This info coming from a group like the Mafia
without any way of exploiting it tells me it's true!
そいつが 恩を売ろうとして流す
マフィアの情報だからこそ➡
真実味がある！
However!
だが！
おっ…｡
おばあぁ！ おぉおっ…｡
いくら真実とはいえ
そんな 最悪の情報を➡
True or not, I can't allow you to bring
such terrible news to Granny Erina out of nowhere like that!
エリナおばあちゃんに
いきなり聞かせたのは 許せねえ！
おびえさせて
悲しませちまったじゃねえか！
And now she's both startled and sad, you dumbass!
このバカたれが！
(ﾏﾌｨｱ)ぐはっ！
50年前のことが…
いまだに 続いているなんて…｡
The madness from fifty years ago... It still hasn't ended...
Are you afraid, Granny?
怖いのか？
おばあちゃん 俺が守ってやる｡
I'll be here to protect you.
違う ジョセフ｡ お前のことだよ｡
That's not it, Joseph!
It's about you!
お前が 巻き込まれていく
運命のことが 怖いのです｡
It's about the destiny you
may end up being caught in that frightens me!
Don't worry about me.
大丈夫だよ｡
If this is my destiny... then so be it!
それが運命なら それに従うぜ！
I wasn't sure what had happened,
but I knew these two definitely had a troubled past.
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)《おいらには
何が何だか 分からないけど➡
この２人は とてつもない過去を
背負っているんだ》
おい スモーキー｡
Hey, Smokey!
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ん～？ 今日は 冷えるな｡
It's freezing today...
This magazine! Take a look!
この雑誌！ ここ見ろよ！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)何だよ？
What is it?
These things, do you think they make
girls' you-know-whats look bigger?!
これ もしかすると
ここ 盛り上げるやつかよ｡
ほへ～！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)なになに？➡
Let's see... "Will make you go from AA cup to C."
｢ＡＡカップが Ｃになる｣
へ～ だまされるぜ！➡
Heh, now they're playing dirty! Better watch out!
気を付けようぜ｡ なっ！
おや？
ペアで １ドル25セントだってよ｡
Huh?
It says it's $1.25 for a pair...
ふぅ…｡
ん？ え… え～と…｡
E-Excuse me...
Ya know, I get the feeling I've seen you somewhere before... Possibly...
はて？ どこかで
見たことがあるような…｡
ないような｡
あんた 以前 どっかで
会ったことないかな？
Perhaps we've already met?
ねえ！ 何で こんなに寒いのに
白い息が出ないんだ？
Hey, how come I can't see
your breath in this freezing cold weather?
And is it just me, or did I catch a glimpse of
something nasty in your mouth? Fangs perhaps?
そして あんた 今 ちらっと
口の中に 牙が見えたような…｡
見えないような｡
とぼけんな この野郎｡
Don't play dumb with me, asshole.
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)フッ…｡➡
街中だろうが 構わん｡➡
I don't care where we do this, Jojo.
ジョジョ！ お前の命をもらう｡
I'm going to end your life before you get
the chance to awaken your true potential!
才能が目覚めんうちにな！
Oh? Is that so?
ほう そうかい｡
(銃声)
(女性１)キャーッ！
I knew he was a little unhinged, but this is insane!
《むちゃなやつとは
分かっていたが！➡
これほどとは！➡
街中でいきなり
どこから 手に入れたのか➡
I don't know where he got it, but he's
going nuts with a Tommy Gun in the middle of the city!
トンプソン機関銃を
ぶっ放した！》
うぉおおおおおお！
(女性２)キャーッ！
Straits, I've been waiting for you to show up!
ストレイツォ！
来るのを待ってたぜ！
I doubt that was enough to kill you...
この程度で
貴様が死ぬとは思わねえが➡
...but for old man Speedwagon...
スピードワゴンじいさんの敵！
宣戦布告だぜ！
...consider this my declaration of war!
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
I'll be the roundabout
♬ I'll be the roundabout
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
The words will make you out 'n' out
I'll spend the day your way
♬ I spend the day away
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬～
♬ The music dance and sing
The music dance and sing
♬ They make
the children really ring
They make the children really ring
♬ Spend the day away
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬ In and around the lake
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
and they stand there
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ Ten true summers
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ I'll be there with you
There with you
Next Episode
This is a vampire?!
I'm gonna tear you to pieces, Straits!
German medical science is number one in the world!
Don't you understand anything?!
Repent for your sins in hell!
Episode 11:
"Game Master"
これが 吸血鬼!?
解体してやる！ ストレイツォ！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)我がドイツの
医学 薬学は 世界一ィィィ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)君は
何も分かっちゃあいないのだ！
地獄で わびろ～！
＜改ざんＢ－ＣＡＳカードによる
不正視聴は➡
刑法により禁じられた犯罪行為＞
＜５年以下の懲役 または➡
50万円以下の
罰金に処せられます＞
＜後悔しても 元には戻せない＞
不正視聴!?